jobkoreausa.com 2016-12-12

# :: 개인정보취급방침

**Privacy Policy**  
 **  **  

This Privacy Policy explains the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information through our web site, jobkoreausa.com. "Personal Information" means information that would allow a party to contact you, including, for example, your full name, address, telephone number, or email address.  

_Submitted Information_. We collect Personal Information about you when you submit information or requests to us (through this website or otherwise). We use your submitted information to send you emails that you have requested, to send your job application and resume to the applicable third party when you apply to certain jobs on our web site, to improve your job search experience on our web site, and for administrative purposes (such as to notify you about changes to this Privacy Policy). In emails we send you, we provide a method to unsubscribe from future emails.  

When you submit your email address as part of our Job Alert application, we use this address for no purpose other than to email you the job alerts that you requested. Your email address is deleted from our database when you remove/unsubscribe from the Job Alert.  

_Browsing Information_. When you use the Jobkoreausa site, our servers (which may be hosted by a third party service provider) may collect information indirectly and automatically (through, for example, the use of your "IP address") about your activities while visiting the site, including the web pages you view and the times you view them and information about the browser you are using.  We do not link browsing information to the Personal Information you submit to us; we use this browsing information to personalize aspects of your search experience (such as enabling you to save your search location on your PC) and for internal purposes such as to help understand how the site is being used and to improve it, and for systems administration purposes. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet. In some cases your IP address stays the same from browser session to browser session; but if you use a consumer internet access provider, your IP address probably varies from session to session.  

_Third Party Cookies_. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.   

_Disclosure of Personal Information_. Although we may disclose aggregated information about the use of our site, that information does not contain Personal Information. We do not disclose Personal Information to third parties in the normal course of operations other than sending your job application and resume to the applicable third party when you apply to certain jobs on our web site. Under certain circumstances, however, we could be legally obligated to disclose information to the government or other third parties and if Jobkoreausa becomes part of another organization, that organization will possess the Personal Information collected by Jobkoreausa and it will assume the rights and obligations regarding your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy.  

_Security_. Jobkoreausa has implemented and follows industry standard measures to protect against unauthorized access to and unlawful interception or processing of Personal Information. However, no internet site can fully eliminate security risks.  

Questions? If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please email us at webmaster@jobkoreausa.com.  

We hope this policy clarifies our procedures regarding your Personal Information. We may amend this policy at any time by sending the amended policy to the email address you provided to us or by posting the amended policy on our site.
